Not sideways!
（火ノ丸(ひのまる)）横じゃねえ！　前へ！
Forward!
（火ノ丸）ンンッ！
（久世(くぜ)）ンッ…
（火ノ丸）ンッ！
（千比路(ちひろ)）２連発！
Another strike!
I can see it right in front of me...
目の前にあるんじゃ
横綱に限りなく近い何かが！
An adversary who's so close
to being a yokozuna!
A victory that I'm willing
to risk my life for!
命を懸けてでも欲しい！　勝利が！
（久世）ウワッ！
Heads together. Both hands on your belt.
（火ノ丸）頭をつけ 両前褌(りょうまえみつ)
これが
たどりついたワシの必殺の型
This is the move I've developed to win!
I won't give you a chance
to start your motion.
（久世）好きに暴れさせはしない
これでも十分に力は出せる
I can still fight back from this position.
My father taught me
this right overhand grip.
父から譲り受けた右上手　天命の型
The move that defines my destiny.
Even one...
（火ノ丸）一瞬でも…
（久世）気を抜けば…
...moment's hesitation...
...and I'll lose!
（２人）殺(や)られる！
Bout 24
"The Dream Continues"
They're evenly matched.
（柴木山(しばきやま)）互角
（天王寺(てんのうじ)）故に 動けへん
Neither can move.
My father once told me
（久世）
いつだったか 父が言っていた
“横綱は孤独だ”と
that yokozunas are solitary.
“己より先に人はなく
道しるべもない”
There is no one ahead of them,
and no signs to guide them.
Each can only rely on himself.
“頼れるのは己のみ”
And he's forced out!
（アナウンス）寄り切り！
横綱に土がつきました！
The yokozuna has been defeated!
Kaoruyama scores a major upset
by forcing out his opponent!
薫山(かおるやま) 大金星！
一気に寄り切りました！
Your father lost.
（美和子）
お父さん 負けちゃったね
Whether he won or lost,
my father never showed emotion,
（久世）勝ち負けによらず
父は いつも平静だったが—
その身から漏れ出る殺気が
僕を緊張させた
but I was unnerved by the
bloodlust I sensed from him.
I strove to be a good child so I wouldn't
interfere with his competitions.
勝負のジャマにならぬよう
いい子でいることを心がけていた
Yamatokuni
父からは—
My father never encouraged or
discouraged me from doing sumo.
相撲を取れとも 取るなとも
言われた覚えはないのだが…
その背中を追うことで 父に
敬意を伝えたかったのかもしれない
Perhaps I followed in his footsteps
to show the respect I had for him.
I prepared myself for it.
それなりに覚悟はあったと思う
I had seen him fight on, even when
he was battered and beaten.
ボロボロになりながらも
戦う姿を見ていたから
I knew other people treated me differently
as the son of a great yokozuna.
周りが僕を大横綱の息子として
扱うことも分かっていた
“偉大な父の名を汚してはならぬ”
I knew I had to uphold
the honor of his name.
It was my duty to become a
great yokozuna like my father.
“父のような
大横綱になるのが使命”
“強くならねば”
I had to become strong.
遠すぎる理想を追い
無心で走る僕は—
Single-mindedly chasing that far-off goal,
相撲を
楽しいと思ったことなどなかった
I never thought of sumo as fun.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
（門弟１）坊っちゃんは すげえな
部屋の誰よりもストイックだ
That boy's incredible.
More stoic than any of the others.
It must be that yokozuna blood in him.
（門弟２）やっぱ横綱の血かね
He's not the same as us.
（部員１）俺らとは違うのさ
（部員２）羨ましいね
I'm jealous.
（久世）ああ…
これが父の言う孤独なのだろう
Yes, this is the solitude
my father spoke of.
だとすれば この道は きっと正しい
Then I must be following the right path.
誰にも理解されずとも
自分以外は 誰もいなくとも—
Even if no one else understands,
even if I must go it alone,
この先に きっと
父のいた横綱という頂が…
I'll find the state of
yokozuna my father attained.
Those who run ahead of others
（大和国(やまとくに)）先頭を走る者は孤独だ
are solitary.
だが 横を見ろ　お前には いたのだ
But look beside you.
You have others with you.
Rivals sharing the same determination
お前と同じ志を持った—
to reach that solitary state.
孤高の頂を
勝ち取らんとするライバルが
Ushio-kun, I'm grateful to you.
（久世）
潮(うしお)君　君には感謝してるんだ
あのとき
僕は自らの意思で 君と立ち合った
I decided to fight you
of my own will that day.
Your soul was burning,
screaming to make itself known.
命を燃やして
自分の存在を叫ぶ君に負けじと—
全力で高め合った
We fought at full strength.
At that moment...
あの瞬間 僕は確かに…
そして 今も…
and even now...
（狩谷(かりや)）チェッ…
He's...
（美和子）あの子…　笑ってる？
smiling?
Are you okay, ma'am?
（門弟３）
大丈夫ッスか？　おかみさん
（美和子）ええ 大丈夫
Yes, I'm fine.
I mustn't look away.
私が目を背けちゃいけないわよね
平気
I'm fine!
I've been the wife of a great
yokozuna for many years.
何年 大横綱の妻やってると
思ってるの？
母として
息子の成長を見届けなくっちゃね
As his mother, I have to see
how much my son has grown.
Fight, Hinomaru!
（火ノ丸の祖母）頑張れ 火ノ丸！
（美和子）えっ？
Your mother's watching!
（祖母）母ちゃんが見とるぞ！
クッ…　ガハッ！
If they just maintain their grips,
（天王寺）
この体格差で組み合い続けても—
the difference in size will
wear Onimaru down faster.
消耗するんは鬼丸(おにまる)のほうや
He's tired from his semifinal bout,
and his left arm is injured, too.
（加納(かのう)）
それに 準決勝の疲労 左腕のケガ
長引けば不利　だが 隙がない
A long bout hurts his chances,
but he doesn't have an opening.
（火ノ丸）
キツイ　すげえ力だ　痛(いて)え
This is tough...
His strength is incredible.
It hurts, and it's hard to breathe.
苦しい！　このままじゃヤバイ！
I need to do something.
Why are you doing sumo?
（恵子(けいこ)）あんたは
なんで相撲をやってるの？
（祖母）また負けたって
He lost again.
小学生のころは
たくさん勝ってたんだけどね
He did so well in elementary school.
It's because he's so small.
（恵子）体が小さいからよね
（祖母）あっ…
（恵子）あの子は優しいから
認めないだろうけど…
He's a good boy, so I'm sure
he doesn't want to think it...
（恵子）死んだ父ちゃんも私も
小さくて ごめんね
I'm sorry your late father and I are so small.
I'm sorry I couldn't give you a bigger body.
大きな体に産んでやれなくて
ごめんね
（火ノ丸）
相撲で勝つと 気持ちがいい
Winning at sumo felt good.
My mom enjoyed seeing me win, too.
She praised me when I did.
母ちゃんも喜んでくれたし
褒めてくれた　うれしかった
It made me happy.
She acted so brave in front of me,
so I wanted to please her even more.
ワシの前では
気丈に振る舞う母ちゃんを—
また喜ばせてやりたかった
母ちゃんのため？
It's all for my mother...
もう母ちゃんは いねえのに
Even though she's gone.
（恵子）違うでしょう　思い出して
No, try to remember.
Why are you doing sumo, Hinomaru?
（恵子）あんたは
なんで相撲をやってるの？　火ノ丸
（アナウンス）東方より
横綱 大和国の土俵入りであります
From the east side, Yokozuna Yamatokuni
is entering the sumo ring.
（しこを踏む音）
（観客たち）よいしょ〜！
Yokozuna!
（桐仁(きりひと)）お前も大和国に憧れたか
ここにいる みんな そうさ
Did you want to be like Yamatokuni, too?
Everyone here did.
大和国みたいになりたくて
始めたんだ
We started sumo so we could be like him.
（火ノ丸）
いや　ワシは ちと違(ちげ)えな
No, it's not quite like that.
（桐仁）火ノ丸　来るぞ！
Hinomaru, here it comes!
Great Serpent Cleaver!
大蛇断(おろちだち)！
It's not just for one reason that I'm here.
（火ノ丸）
ここにいる理由なんて絞りきれねえ
いや　ワシは ちと違えな
No, it's not quite like that.
I'm thinking of how much fun it'd be
to throw a huge yokozuna like that.
あのでっけえ横綱を
ぶん投げたら—
どんだけ気持ちいいだろうなって
思ったんじゃ
（火ノ丸）初期衝動も 負の感情も
My initial motivation...
My feeling of loss...
The expectations and my obligations...
期待も恩義も
みんなとの日々も
母ちゃんも 全部ひっくるめて…
The time I've spent with my team...
and for the sake of my mother, too!
（沙田(さだ)）妬(や)けるね
He's burning up.
（火ノ丸）相撲が好きだから
ワシは ここにいる！
I love sumo! That's why I'm here!
火ノ丸が 試合中に笑ってる
Hinomaru is smiling in a bout.
（礼奈(れいな)）ハッ…
そこだー！
There!
Close the gap,
（柴木山）
引き付け 隙間をなくして
上体が伸びたところを下から…
then when his upper body is extended,
come up from beneath!
（桐仁たち）押せーっ！
Push!
Yes, yes!
よし！　よし！
（駿海(しゅんかい)）無差別級ゆえに
生まれる ありえない光景
It's something that can only
happen with no weight classes.
The smaller contender rises up
and thrills the spectators!
小さき者の反逆が
見る者をたぎらせる
引いた！？　土俵際だぞ！
He pulled back?
He's at the edge of the ring!
A spirit that cannot be contained
in his small body...
（大和国）
その小さな体に収まりきらぬ闘気(とうき)
A national treasure, the future of sumo.
国宝　相撲の未来か
But Sosuke is no different.
だが それは草介(そうすけ)も同じ
Seeing size and speed
（大和国）大きさ 速さ—
圧倒的フィジカルの躍動も
また相撲の醍醐味(だいごみ)
and overwhelming physical energy
is part of the appeal of sumo.
久世が左四つ…
Kuze's using a left underarm grip.
This isn't all.
（久世）こんなものじゃない
父の…
僕の相撲は こんなもんじゃないぞ
The sumo my father and I
share is more than this.
I'm right here!
僕は ここにいるぞ！
New Great Serpent Cleaver!
Right
Overarm
Throw
Right
Overarm
Throw
True
Great
Serpent
Cleaver
True
Great
Serpent
Cleaver
Reverse Hundred Demon Takedown!
Reverse
Hundred
Demon
Takedown
Reverse
Hundred
Demon
Takedown
They're doing throws on each other.
（咲(さき)）投げの打ち合い！
（天王寺）反応が速すぎる
His reaction was too quick.
He was expecting that.
読んでいたな
I figured you'd counter.
（火ノ丸）
お前なら返すと思っていた
お前の強さを信じていた！
I believed in your strength!
（礼奈）堀(ほり)ちゃん　ありがとうね
（千鶴子(ちづこ)）えっ？
Hori-chan, thank you.
I probably wouldn't be here
if it weren't for you.
（礼奈）堀ちゃんがいなかったら
私 多分 ここにいなかった
I didn't know anything about sumo.
相撲のことなんて
何も知らなかった
I didn't know anything and made fun of it.
何も知らないのに バカにしてた
But...
でも 間近で見た それは—
When I'm this close...
Every time those carefully
sculpted bodies crash,
鍛え抜かれた筋肉の塊が
ぶつかり合う度 すごい音がして
they make an incredible sound.
In a single moment,
they use countless maneuvers.
一瞬の中に
無数の駆け引きがあって
I thought it was embarrassing
that they wore only belts,
恥ずかしいと思ってた廻(まわ)し姿も—
今では その飾らなさが
ちょっとだけカッコイイと思ってる
but I'm starting to see
how aesthetic it is.
そして 相撲を知れば知るほど
分かる あいつの強さ
And the more I learn about
sumo, the more I understand
how strong he is!
小さな体で 何度はじかれても
向かっていく その姿に…
Now matter how many times he's knocked
back, he still rises up again.
（歓声）
（礼奈）みんな 目を…
It captivates the crowd's eyes and hearts!
心を奪われるんだ
（礼奈）好き…
（千鶴子）ハッ…
This is love.
Love for Hinomaru's sumo.
私は あんたの…
火ノ丸の相撲が好きだよ
僕が… 負ける？
Am I... going to lose?
（久世）
負けたくない　早く組み止めないと
I don't want to lose!
I need to stop him.
Shake him!
揺さぶれー！
ああ…　僕は今 真剣勝負を…
I'm fighting a serious...
sumo bout!
相撲を取っている！
I feel how close death is.
死を隣に感じている　最高だ
It's incredible.
My limits are finally being tested.
初めて試される己の限界
For me to beat him now...
彼に勝つには 今の僕では…
I can't simply imitate my father.
父の真似事(まねごと)では足りないんだ
I must surpass Yamatokuni!
大和国を超えるんだ！
（久世）神を超えるんだ！
I must surpass a god!
He's pulling him down!
（桐仁）強引！
（千比路）耐えろー！
Stay strong!
There is no thought to his movements.
（大和国）考えて動いたのではない
稽古場だけでは磨けぬものがある
This is something that cannot
be taught in a training hall.
そう 本能！
Yes, instinct!
I see.
（久世）そうか
これが高め合うってことなんだな
This is what it means to
drive each other higher.
God
Body
Hammer
God
Body
Hammer
Pulling Body Slam! God Body Hammer!
〝呼び戻し〞 身神槌(みかづち)！
An illusion?
幻影？
Which is crazier?
（四方田(よもだ)）場数の差か
I'm small, so I've had to worry
and work harder than anyone.
（火ノ丸）小せえから
誰より悩んだし 苦労もした
But I've also thought more about sumo, too.
でも おかげで
誰より相撲のことを考えたし—
This body has let me enjoy
sumo more than anyone.
この体のおかげで
誰より相撲を楽しめたんじゃ
ありがとうよ 母ちゃん
Thank you, Mom.
His arm...
腕が…
（佑真(ゆうま)）体力が…
（千比路）もう限界
Is he out of strength?
Is this it?
How cruel can this get?
（蛍(けい)）どこまで残酷なんですか？
I'll hate you, god of sumo!
（柴木山）恨むぜ 相撲の神さまよ
（礼奈）クッ…
（小関(おぜき)）グッ…
グオーッ！
This body has overcome
every obstacle in its way!
（火ノ丸）何度でも
限界を超えてくれる この体が—
I'm proud of it!
ワシの誇りじゃ！
And I'll throw down
（火ノ丸）相撲の神さま？
any god of sumo that says otherwise!
そんなもん ワシが
ぶん投げてやるわ！
Right
Underarm
Throw
Right underarm throw! Demon Wheel!
Right
Underarm
Throw
Demon
Wheel
（小関）いけー！　潮！
Go, Ushio!
（火ノ丸）ワシは潮火ノ丸
I am Ushio Hinomaru.
In order to reach yokozuna,
横綱へと至る道として—
I must become the strongest
high school sumo wrestler!
高校相撲の頂点を
取らんとする者じゃ！
（審判）東の勝ち！
East side wins!
Listen to that cheering.
（駿海）すげえ歓声だ
（柴木山）ええ　僕にも見えますよ
Yeah, and even I can see...
the cascading cushions.
乱れ舞う座布団が
ハァ…
（大和国）
息子を負かしたのが 彼で良かった
I'm glad that he was
the one who defeated my son.
いずれ負けを知るべきだとは
思っていましたが—
He had to experience defeat someday.
その先 どうするか その答えも
同時に見せてもらいましたから
Now I can see
what he'll do next at the same time.
Let's go.
（美和子）行きましょう
（門弟３）うん？
You did it, Hinomaru.
やったな　火ノ丸
I'm sure your mother hears the applause, too.
おふくろさんにも
この歓声は きっと届いてるぞ
（火ノ丸）ワシ１人では
とても ここまで来れなかった
I couldn't have made it here alone.
強敵たちに磨かれ…
I've been blessed with strong
opponents who tested me.
協力者たちに恵まれ…
そして 仲間たちに支えられ…
And...
My teammates supported me.
ここまで来れた
When your dream comes true...
（恵子）
お前の夢が かなうとき—
I may not be with you, but I'll be watching.
そばには いてやれないけど
見てるからね
雲の上から
お前のこと見てるからね
I'll be watching from the clouds.
（火ノ丸）
まだ夢が かなったわけじゃねえ
My dream hasn't come true yet.
But...
でも…
（ナレーション）“相撲”…
Sumo...
土俵上で 廻しのみを身につけ 戦う
日本古来の武道であり…
Battles waged since ancient times in Japan.
（審判）礼！
Bow.
It is one of the few combat sports
without weight classes.
（ナレーション）
数少ない“無差別級”の格闘技
Thus, larger and heavier student sumo
wrestlers have a distinct advantage.
ゆえに “大きく”
“重く”ある者が絶対有利
Among those giants, there was one
who desired to become a yokozuna.
巨漢ひしめく中 それでも
横綱を目指さんとする彼の体は—
His body was small, sturdy, and...
あまりにも小さく たくましく
そして…
（審判）東の勝ち！
（歓声）
East side wins!
...dignified.
（ナレーション）気高い
（アナウンス）
以上 ３対２で 大太刀(おおだち)高校の勝ち！
The match is over.
Odachi High School wins 3-2.
（礼奈）みんな おめでとう
（火ノ丸）ウオッ！
Congratulations, guys!
I'm crying because you cried!
（礼奈）あんたが泣くから…
（火ノ丸）ウヘヘッ…
Thanks for cheering for me.
（火ノ丸）応援ありがとうな
Yuma, you're the best in Japan, too!
（礼奈）佑真も日本一だよ
Yeah.
１人で やってた相撲部だったけど
最後の最後で 最高のチームで…
This was a one-man sumo club...
But now, it's the strongest team of all!
Sumo...
すも… 取り… あり…
（小関の泣き声）
Thank...
Guys, thank you so much!
みんな　本当に ありがとう！
そっか　このチームで
試合を戦うのは もう…
I see... They won't compete
as a team anymore.
Now we wait to see if Hinomaru qualified
for the All-Japan National Championships.
あとは 火ノ丸が全日本大会の枠に
入れるかどうかだな
（火ノ丸）ああ
（柴木山）心配ないさ
Yeah.
Not to worry.
（火ノ丸）あっ…
（桐仁）親方！
Master.
He did his part. There's no way they won't
take him after all that cheering. Right?
（柴木山）結果は出した
あの歓声で選ばれなかったら
ウソだろう　なあ？
（桐仁）あっ…　大和国親方
Master Yamatokuni!
３年ぶり …かな
It's been three years, I believe.
あっ 覚えててくれたんスね
You remembered me.
（火ノ丸）“３年先の稽古をしろ”
"Practice for three years from now."
あの言葉を支えに
今日まで耐え忍ぶことができました
Those words supported me and
allowed me to endure until today.
Thank you.
ありがとうございました
（大和国）さっきの試合
（火ノ丸）うん？
That match...
君たちは
新たな時代の到来を見せてくれた
Your team showed us the future of sumo.
大相撲は 君を待っている
The pro league will be waiting for you.
相撲の未来のために
変わらぬ精進を
For the future of sumo,
using that same diligence,
practice for three years from
now, Ushio Hinomaru-kun.
３年先の稽古をしなさい
潮火ノ丸君
（狩谷）団体優勝逃(のが)したから
栄大(えいだい)に残るなんて言うなよ 草介
Don't go saying you'll stay at Eiga High
because we lost the team tournament, Sosuke.
来年は 俺たちで優勝してみせる
てめえは さっさと先に行け！
We'll still win next year.
You keep moving forward.
This disappointment...
（久世）この悔しさは…
（狩谷）うん？
It may be something I can only
experience in grade-level sumo.
（久世）学生相撲の団体戦でしか
味わえないものなのかもしれない
It's odd to say after I've lost, but...
負けて言うのも何だけど
栄大に入って良かった
I'm glad I came to Eiga High.
そうか！
I see!
The National High School Sumo
Team Tournament champions...
（アナウンス）全国高等学校
相撲選手権大会 団体優勝—
Odachi High School from Chiba!
千葉県立 大太刀高校！
Thank you for your support!
（小関）
ご声援 ありがとうございました！
（千鶴子）
全日本選手権へ出場を
果たした潮君は—
Ushio-kun competed in the All-Japan
National Championships.
準決勝で
天王寺さんに敗れ—
He lost to Tennoji-san in the
semifinal and took third place.
３位となりました
優勝は天王寺さん
Tennoji-san was the champion.
幕下十五枚目付出(つけだし)の
資格を手にしました
He earned the right to become
a fifteenth-ranked makushita.
Your left arm wasn't at full strength.
左腕が
本調子やなかったんやろけどな
これで２勝１敗
勝ち越しや
That makes us 2-1. I'm leading.
Still, we'll be trading wins
and losses from now on.
まあ
これからイヤでも—
勝ち負けを繰り返すんや
For now, I'm a makushita...
とりあえず 俺は幕下から
お前は三段目からや
おめでとう！
And you're a sandanme. Congratulations.
Glad to have you.
よろしくな
ウッス！
Yeah.
After the Inter-High,
Kuze-kun entered the pro league.
（千鶴子）久世君は
インターハイのあと—
角界入りを表明
He joined in time for the
September tournament.
ひと足早く 九月場所で
初土俵を踏みました
You're just a sandanme,
but your size doesn't matter.
三段目からだが
同じく体格は不問
The door to your dream has opened.
君の夢への扉は開かれた
Welcome to the pro league, Hinomaru.
大相撲へ ようこそ
火ノ丸
Thank you.
（火ノ丸）
お世話になります
But he only earned his place for one year.
（千鶴子）
けれど 付出資格の期限は１年
行使するには 潮君は
高校を辞めなくてはなりません
In order to keep it,
Ushio-kun had to drop out of high school.
それは つまり—
That meant saying goodbye to the
Odachi High School sumo club.
大太刀高校相撲部との別れを
意味していました
Oh, Ushio-kun is a splendid student!
（校長）いやぁ
潮君は本当に すばらしい生徒でね
これからも
全校を挙げて 応援するからね
Our school will continue to cheer him on!
（火ノ丸）ウヘヘッ…　頑張ります
I'll do my best.
（柴木山）ハハッ…　疲れたか？
I'll bet you're tired.
It'll take time to get used
to this type of thing.
こういうことにも
少しずつ慣れていかんとな
実際 大相撲に入ったら
こんなもんでは済まないぞ
It's even worse once
you're in the pro league.
Especially for you, since your
height makes you stand out.
特に お前は身長で目立つからな
（火ノ丸）はい 分かっとります
Yes, sir. I understand.
Also that the attention can be fleeting.
注目されとるうちが
花じゃということも
It's been so dizzying up to today.
（火ノ丸）ただ
本当に 今日まで目まぐるしくて
部長と佑真は受験
The captain and Yuma are studying for exams.
The others are busy with
training and other things.
残ったみんなも 出稽古やら
何やらで慌ただしくて
It's a shame I wasn't able
to say a proper goodbye.
ちゃんと
別れの挨拶ができんかったのが—
少し心残りですね
ウヘヘッ…　大丈夫です
But it's okay!
I'll tell them by performing
well in the pro league!
プロで活躍することが 何よりの
挨拶じゃと思っとりますから
さあ 行きましょう
Okay, let's go!
何だい？　ラブレターでも？
What's that? A love letter?
ウヘヘッ…　似たようなもんです
The next best thing.
Challenge Letter
（火ノ丸）すみません！
ちょっと寄らせてください
Excuse me! Let me take care of something!
It's the captain's sumo ring
that was destroyed!
壊されて なくなったはずの
部長の土俵！
（佑真）小関に教わりながら
作ったんだけどよ　大変なんだな
Ozeki explained how to make it.
It was still a pain, though.
It was a regret of mine for so long,
but I'm glad it's here now.
ずっと心残りだった
でも 間に合って良かった
Help me train before you go gallivanting off!
遠くに行っちまう前に
胸貸してくれや
That's not right.
（蛍）違うでしょう
（火ノ丸）うん？
He's not helping us train.
We're doing this for real.
（蛍）胸借りるんじゃない
ガチで やるんですよ
Damn straight!
（千比路）…たり前(めえ)よ！
（桐仁）
…でなきゃ 意味ないからな
What's the point otherwise?
It's our farewell present.
（佑真）餞別(せんべつ)代わりだ
The Dachi High sumo club's
serious style you helped create.
お前が育てたダチ高相撲部の
本気の相撲　しっかりと受け取れ！
You'd better be ready!
Guys...
（火ノ丸）みんな…
Farewell sumo, huh? You must be crazy,
as cold as it is out here.
送別相撲ね
まったく 寒いのに よくやるよ
（火ノ丸）ウヘヘッ…
Who do you think you're talking to?!
誰に言うとるんじゃ！？
I'm strong!
ワシは強いぞ！
Get ready for this!
覚悟しておけよ！